THE FLOWERS OF EVIL - BAUDELAIRE
FOR ALL THE BOYS AND GIRLS
STRUGGLING THROUGH ADOLESCENCE
AND FOR THE BOYS AND GIRLS WE ONCE WERE
Ah, dear Baudelaire...
I am confined.
I am confined in this town
surrounded by mountains.
Empty alleyways.
Let's go to the arcade.
Closed shutter doors.
Did you catch GLAY's new song?
The boring route to school.
Can I burn it onto my MD?
Why is all the metal
in this town rusted?
Why does this town...
suffocate me so badly?
In the confinement of this town,
literature is the only thing
that teaches me anything real.
And my only source of hope?
That is...
...an angel.
On your marks.
SAEKI
Go, go!
There's the angel,
spreading her wings to soar,
at this very moment.
Your smile is a ray of sun in the spring.
You run and a gentle breeze follows.
Saeki,
98 points!
You did a great job.
Thank you very much.
That's amazing!
Best grade in multiple subjects?
You're in your own league, Nanako.
It's nothing special.
- See? Look at mine.
- Really?
You are special!
Your intelligence is
like a beautiful pearl...
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
- Hey!
- Hey, stop!
52 points?
Come on, you gotta do better than that.
All that reading, for what?
What is this weird book anyway?
The Flowers of Evil!
It's Baudelaire!
As if you'd understand its excellence!
You're looking down on me, aren't you?
Nakamura.
Nakamura!
Answer me. Respond!
Yeah, I'm here.
Nakamura, you got
the worst grade in class.
Zero points.
Explain yourself.
Why did you leave all the answers blank?
Say something!
Once you're in the real world,
you won't get--
Shut up,
you shit bug.
You are speaking to your teacher.
How dare you call me "shit bug"!
Come to the faculty room
after school. Understood?
All right.
Next... Muraoka!
Come on. Hurry up!
Nakamura's insane!
Like, you don't know what she's thinking.
- She gives me the creeps.
- Right?
Honestly, it was a bit refreshing.
Seeing Shimoyama shaking and all.
Man, I'd never want to date
a girl like that.
- Agreed.
- What?
Why are you acting superior?
- No one would want to date you.
- Good point.
How dare you. You're no better than me!
What? No, that's not true!
:cue
I... I read books!
You think you can understand literature?
Reading books doesn't
make you special or anything!
Besides, no one has even noticed!
Wait...
I forgot my book.
I'm gonna go get it.
- Hey, are you running away?
- No!
- I really forgot it!
- Hey, you wimp!
He totally ran away.
I suppose...
Saeki hasn't noticed
that I'm reading a book like this.
SAEKI
Her gym clothes...
Idiot! What am I thinking!
My feelings for Saeki are honorable.
They're pure.
I don't have any sinful thoughts...
at all.
Not a bit.
There's no way.
I don't have any immoral desires.
I definitely...
Definitely...
Kasuga.
It smells like...
shampoo...
It's not like that!
Takao?
What are you talking about?
Those books in your room!
You'd better clean them up!
No, no, no.
It was just a coincidence.
This was an unintentional accident.
:cue
Like The Flowers of Evil...
for real...
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 1
Saeki's gym clothes were missing
when she got to school this morning.
Does anyone know anything about this?
It's a pervert! Right, guys? Right?
If you know something,
make sure you come and tell me!
Understood?
I am a sinner.
I want to go somewhere far away.
Somewhere... far away.
But...
In this confined town,
there's nowhere I can run to.
111.8 MILES TO THE SEA
Saeki...
I'm sorry.
I will atone for this sin
for the rest of my life.
Even when I'm an old man.
What are you doing?
Huh?
By the way,
you're always reading a book, aren't you?
What?
How do you know that?
Because I sit behind you.
Oh.
On top of that,
it's a weird book that nobody would know.
Why is that?
Well...
I bet normal people
can't understand, but--
Wait. What?
What?
Give me a ride.
To the other side of that mountain.
What?
But, well, I mean...
Why?
'Cause I want to go there.
What? Like...
You know, I have to go now, so--
Huh?
Kasuga.
The thing is...
I saw you.
I saw you...
steal...
Saeki's gym clothes.
It smells like...
shampoo...
What?
If you don't want me to tell everyone,
you'd better get going.
He ran away.
:cue
YOUNG BOY TURNS TO CRIME
In recent years,
we've seen an increase
in heinous incidents by teenagers...
LONELINESS
INNER DEMONS
...as juvenile crimes intensify.
Why are boys with no record
of delinquency committing such offences?
Takao.
What's wrong?
What? No, nothing.
I'll turn myself in.
Before Nakamura exposes me...
I'll confess my sins...
to Saeki herself.
All right, then, some announcements.
As I always say, you guys,
don't cause trouble.
Baudelaire...
...bestow strength
upon me!
Sir.
What is it, Kasuga?
Saeki.
It's about your gym clothes.
I'm the one who took them.
I'm sorry!
Kasuga...
You've told me the truth...
Thank you.
Kasuga...
you're a true man of virtue.
All right, that's all.
It's impossible!
How could I turn myself in?
COME TO THE LIBRARY AFTER SCHOOL
DON'T RUN AWAY TODAY
LIBRARY
Why did you run away yesterday?
That must mean you don't mind
if I tell everyone, right?
No, it doesn't!
You spineless coward.
Filthy rat!
:cue
I wasn't trying to steal it!
I just ended up taking it home,
- I meant to give it back and apologize--
- Kasuga?
What?
You wanted to talk?
Well... I...
Kasuga,
don't you have
something important to tell her?
What?
By any chance,
do you know something...
about my gym clothes?
No! Well, you see--
Sorry!
Way to go, Kasuga.
You went dead center.
What?
I'm ruined...
Why would you do that?
Tell me,
how do you feel right now?
Write me an essay
about how you feel right now.
An... an essay?
What the heck do you mean?
By tomorrow.
See you after school.
No way I'd ever write that...
How?
How did I end up in this situation?
SECOND YEAR, CLASS ONE
- Maeda.
Muraoka.
Hey, everybody!
Teach is gonna get the police involved
about Saeki's gym clothes!
It's a serious case now! How crazy!
Hey, cut it out, Yamada!
I'm sorry, Nanako.
Ignore him.
Yeah.
:cue
Come on, show me the essay.
You don't have it?
What's that?
A book of poems by Baudelaire.
The Flowers of Evil.
It's the book I love the most.
What?
Dark emotions billow throughout this book.
It's philosophy that people
in this town could never understand.
Baudelaire took the malice
all of us secretly harbor
and spelled it all out in this book!
This is who I am.
This is my ess--
Shut it, shit bug.
I was expecting...
...a messy...
and gushy...
exhibition of your true self, Kasuga.
I wanted you to spill out
everything in this essay!
You buried your face in Saeki's boobs,
sniffed her gym clothes over and over,
and rubbed them
all over your body, didn't you?
You know that you're a total,
utter pervert, Kasuga!
What the heck?
This doesn't make any sense!
What's wrong with you, Nakamura?
I... I'm not.
I didn't rub them all over my body!
Saeki is my goddess!
She's my muse, my femme fatale,
my Mary, and my Venus.
She will be, forever!
I'll burn this damned thing
in the incinerator!
What the!
By the way, that thing we talked about...
my big brother has one.
- Hey guys...
- Seriously?
Do you know where Kasuga is?
- Oh... Kasuga?
- Yeah.
No clue.
Okay. Thanks. Bye.
What? Hey, wait! What?
Stop it!
What?
Wait, stop!
Ah!
Ah! No! Somebody!
:cue
Do you want people to see this?
LIBRARY - CLOSED
Hey, wait!
Wait!
Hey, wait! Stop!
This...
is your true self. Isn't it, Kasuga?
Fine.
I won't tell anyone.
Because, Kasuga,
you're special.
Special?
In return...
I want you...
to make a contract with me.
What?
A contract?
TO BE CONTINUED
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
Kasuga agrees
to a mysterious contract.
Through a twist of fate,
he manages to score
a date with Saeki, but...
Next time, on episode two.
The contract with Nakamura
weighs heavily on Kasuga.
Translated by Yuka Kristi